

Hvderabad, India

□ (+91) 9515906959 |
□ rahulmora007@gmail.com |
□ rahul mora

Summary.

A Computer Science graduate with 2 years of experience in the field of Software Engineering. Currently working as Soft- ware Development Engineer in JP Morgan Chase & Co. Customer-oriented and structured method of working, focused on quality and maintainability. High motivated to work in team, both comfortable to big companies as in small teams.

Skills

Programming Languages Java C, Python, Javascript

Frameworks And Libraries Spring -boot, Spring Batch, Angular, Node JS, Flask Cloud Technologies Cloud-Foundry, Amazon Web Services(AWS) **Databases** MySql, Oracle, No-Sql databases like MongoDB

Tools Kubernetes, Spark, Pentaho ETL tool, CI/CD(Jenkins), Jasper Reporting Tool

Education

Chaitanya Bharathi Institute Of Technology Hyderabad

BTECH IN COMPUTER SCIENCE (CSE)

August 2016 - July 2020

CGPA - 7.25

Work Experience _____

JP Morgan Chase & Co Hyderabad, India

SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT ENGINEER

Aug. 2020 - Present

- · My Responsibilities are designing and developing highly scalable applications which could load and process files containing millions of records by maintaining standard coding practices
- Developed an Excel file row-by-row Parser to read and process large excel files efficiently
- · Innovated the report generation process of our system which increased efficiency by 4 times Worked on Date-Processing tools like Spark, AWS **FMR**
- Worked with Data-Engineering team closely and gained skill-set and knowledge in that field
- Gained experience on ETL tools like Pentaho
- Worked on Job scheduling tools like control-m which are used to build loosely coupled components
- Have been exposed to modern cloud technologies like Kubernetes

JPMorgan Chase & Co

Hyderabad, India

Jan. 2020 - Jul. 2020

SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT ENGINEER INTERN

- Part of a team which builds reconciliation systems
- Developed an Angular & springboot application to track the reconciliation process
- Developed a spring batch application to load huge files into the Database
- Worked in Agile methodology and worked on tools like JIRA, confluence
- · Understood the impact of unit test cases and also worked on writing unit test cases for several applications to understand their functionalities

Caravel Al Hyderabad, India

CONTENT STRATEGIST INTERN

May. 2019 - June. 2019

· Caravel AI has an online learning platform called Keats. For keats, I Worked as a content writer for Data science course

Achievements __

- Recognized by the technical head of the sub-lob for my efforts in scaling up the application by 4 times
- Stood Third in a Hackathon conducted by Women Techmakers Orgaization

Extracurricular Activity _

JPMC Code-For-Good Hackathon

Hyderabad

SUBJECT MATTER EXPERT 2020 2021

• Worked as a SME for Cloud-technologies and Spring-boot to help the participants

RAHUL RESUME

2021

ALUMINI SME/ MENTOR

 $\bullet \ \ \text{Worked as a Mentor \& SME for young graduates who joined in the organization as part of SEP program in 2021}$

RAHUL RESUME 2